This is Bongiorno Toggy.
This time I'm here at Fukuoka Civic Hall.
This hall will close its doors in March 2025.
the curtain will come down on 60 years of history.
It's one of my favorite halls in Japan.
Actually, it was chosen as one of the 100 best halls in Japan by an acoustician.
The sound is great.
For example, Tatsuro Yamashita likes to perform at both Sun Palace and Shimin Kaikan.
Tatsuro Yamashita, for example, would not want to give a concert in a bigger place.
They are halls with excellent acoustics.
But they're both aging, and they're going to be rebuilt, and they won't be open until next March, so it's a little sad.
Today, we're going to have a concert at Fukuoka Civic Hall.
Today, at the Fukuoka Civic Hall, we're hosting DIG Fukuoka, the weekly Thursday show on FM Fukuoka, with Toggy's partner, Ueda of the idol Batten Shoujo-tai.
Riko Ueda of the idol group Batten Shoujo-tai.
Riko Ueda is a member of the idol group Batten Shoujo-tai, and she's going to give a one-woman live performance.
How can old men, including me, who are new to idol concerts, enjoy a concert?
I wondered how we, the old men who are new to idol concerts, including myself, would be able to enjoy the concert.
I'm not sure I can do it alone.
So two more uncles are coming.
The three of us will be going undercover.
This show is all about driving safely and making everyone smile!
Presented by Corolla Fukuoka and Spirit of Zero Greener
Kitakyushu City, designated by the OECD as Asia's first green growth city, is home to the startup company Greener.
In a resource-recycling society, the concept of waste does not exist
Green Consumers backed by Greener
Solo live performance in Fukuoka, my hometown.
Also, we are celebrating our 9th anniversary, so we will be receiving a lot of flowers, but we are not going to be the only ones.
FM Fukuoka
From DIG Fukuoka Ichido
Stand
From FM Fukuoka
We are sending them to you.
Fukuoka Civic Hall is almost 60 years old, so this is the stage.
This is the stage, this is the catering room, this is the dressing room, this is the massage area.
This is the backstage area.
I have great memories of the late Mr. Kang.
I used to hold concerts at the Fukuoka Civic Auditorium.
I used to talk with his family after the concert.
There were various caterers.
This staff is also invited.
Fine muscat grapes.
They're very expensive, aren't they? Very expensive.
But not too expensive.
And this Mr. Banraku... from Miyazaki.
They're collaborating with an eel shop in Miyazaki.
I have to try it.
This and the kabayaki from the eel restaurant, Muchan manju.
Fukuoka's soul food!
I guess they're coming.
Oh, wow!
I knew it! Fukuoka's got it!
I'll try it right away.
Grilled onigiri style.
And unagi (eel) too.
The day of Saturday is a little late this year.
Delicious!
I could eat this in one bite.
It's so good as a side dish!
I like ham and eggs the best, too. Ham and eggs with mayonnaise.
Yum!
And the massage, too!
Mr. Togi said he'd like to try it, too.
Hello.
May I? Are you sure? Just a little bit.
Just a little bit.
We're all going to do it?
Isn't this a bit like Eikichi Yazawa?
He's a big hottie.
Ouch, ouch, ouch, my right leg hurts.
Oh!
It's interesting from a picture point of view, isn't it?
They come in from both sides like this.
Together?
Yes, sir.
If this side is here, is it hard to get to the next side?
Can you do it?
Can you get this one here?
Put it where you can.
Okay. Okay.
Let's see if we can get it to this point. Okay.
Yes, yes, yes.
If you could just adjust it.
This is the stage, isn't it?
Oh, ho ho ho, it's going, it's going, it's going.
This is a quick rehearsal.
Good morning.
My guess is Riko Ueda in red.
Or rather, her partner.
I'm going.
Wow.
Two.
From the end of the voice to the head when she's a good miya.
Yes!
The doors are now open.
So we've arrived at
FM Fukuoka Gau personality and well-known
Kuro-chan, aka Kurokawa Osamu.
Hello. I'm Osamu Kurokawa.
Thank you for coming on such short notice.
We're matching. This one's red.
Red.
Different members have different colors.
Red... the barber's.
We wear matching shirts to idol concerts.
Recently, I've been to a lot of field days and polly parties... from the very beginning.
I'm a beginner.
I've been discharged from the hospital in March, and my fans are coming to see me.
No. 3, I have to do a lot of things.
We have to do a lot of things. You mean learn how to have fun?
Yes, I guess we were a little prejudiced
We're having a great live party.
It's a very exciting live radio show.
The music, lighting, and VGM are amazing!
I could lose about 3 kgs.
Really?
I'll take a picture before the show.
Let's do it!
One more person, Machida-kun, will join us for the show.
I'm looking forward to it.
My analysis... every Thursday, everyone gathers at the live radio studio to watch Riko.
People come from as far away as Tokyo.
My impression at that time was, of course, that it was mainly men, but there were also couples, couples and couples.
But there were also couples, couples, and women only.
I was impressed by the variety of impressions.
I think there are various textures to this cuteness.
But the "Battentional's And" members are really like this.
For example, I love Momoclo.
When I first saw her, I thought she was just one step away from me.
Because she's small.
From around junior high school.
Riko was in her teens when I first saw her.
That's when I started seeing them.
Not as a parental figure, but...
But as a relative uncle.
I felt like I was rooting for you.
I'm sure you all have that feeling.
I think you all might have that feeling.
That's why we sometimes want to support each other as a family.
I think of her as my sister.
I think of her as my daughter.
Or grandchildren.
I think some of you are cheering for her.
Please come in... I'm talking about the women who come to the studio.
Of course, they come to see us.
There are two plus Hayato Machida.
This is Hayato Machida, and this is Obake-san.
They'll be here soon.
It's the first time for the three of us to be in an idol group.
You have to be careful.
There's nothing I have to be careful about.
Anyway, enjoy yourself from the bottom of your heart
I'm going to enjoy it from here
Let me worry about my voice too
Is that it, Black?
Can you do Dendelaru?
Yes, I can't.
LOL.
Let's learn it now.
We have one hour left.
Denderalieu can...
I'm already repeating this.
Denderalieu is
I can already do it at Meiji.
Dance Black will be fine.
That's right.
Also...
If you dance freely...
Dance freely?
Like this.
Okay.
It's yellow to see.
Are you sure you want to show your face?
Where are you from today?
I'm from Yokohama.
Yokohama.
It's twilight.
I knew it. I heard it on FM Pokal.
I knew you were Toggy.
Of course I did.
I'm so glad.
People are coming to see you today.
They say he's coming in deck red.
I'm looking forward to it.
It's not a matter of time.
What are you going to do today? After this.
After this, we'll all be together for now, about 50 people.
50 people?
There will be a launch party for 50 people?
Thank you very much.
Do you want to come?
I'd like to go.
That's a lot of people.
This street.
You've booked such a big venue?
Yes, we have.
It's amazing.
Midorikichi?
Midorikichi.
Where are you from?
I'm from Yamaguchi Prefecture.
Good, good, good.
What's that?
The one with Riko and Soggy on the radio.
Thank you very much.
Midorikichi.
It's coming down.
Boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom.
That's the wrestler.
Road safety, right?
Let's have a good time.
Yes, sir.
Okay, thank you very much.
Bye, guys.
Wait.
Bye.
Amazing.
Oh, wow!
You're here!
Wow, wow, that's a little on the small side.
What's with my Neva?
I'm looking forward to working with you guys.
Nice to meet you.
Foundation style, boom!
Nice to meet you. - Nice to meet you.
How are you feeling? I'm feeling good.
Okay, please introduce yourselves one by one.
I'm Satoko Ueda, a black belt in karate and a white belt in speaking, and I'm the MC.
I'm Megumi Yanagimi, Princess of Level Lion.
I'm Sakura Seta, the president of the Kyushu Food Culture Lovers Association.
Yes, I'm Ai Seima, the dance leader of the "Three Thousand People Who Asked for a Sweet Potato"!
Yes, I bring you a pink Halo to the blue earth!
I am Blue Leader, everyone's Chair Leader!
Yes, it's combined soul time!
I am Ina Harumaki, an official supporter. Pleased to meet you.
So, Riko, I've been watching you since the rehearsal,
No, really,
Really?
Mr. Lolly thought so.
I was surprised.
The only idol I've ever seen is Perfume.
Yes, yes, yes. So it was best to be alone at the Perfume show. I didn't know what to do.
I'm going to enjoy myself to the fullest today, and it's going to be like a rave party at the venue.
I'm looking forward to the dance-dance, the sound is really cool, and the production was really cool.
Thank you very much.
I'll be there.
Ai, Riku, Hina, Sakura
Miu, Toki, this is our stage!
Let's go!
Fashion
Dance
Well, good luck!
I'll be entertained.
I look forward to working with you.
Thank you very much.
It's here, it's here, it's here.
Here they come.
Thank you.
Rice planting?
This is where we started.
Let me introduce myself.
I'm half farmer, half entertainer.
Half farmer, half entertainer.
I'm Hayato Machida.
You're running for election?
You're going too far.
I'm Hayato Machida.
Are you already a veteran of idol concerts?
No, I've been to quite a few, though I'm not sure if I should say this in front of all the fans and members.
Oh, that's right.
I've been to quite a few.
Wow, quite a lot.
Not only Nukeso? I'm mainly here for Nukeso and the others. I never really went through idol shows in my youth.
But when I was in an event with Batten Shoujo-tai, I thought they were no longer an idol but a punk band.
The music was pretty rock at first, so I joined because I liked the songs.
It was like a rock band's live show was more energetic.
In Korea, live performances are very energetic.
So you are going to enjoy yourself to the fullest today?
That's right.
For those of you who are watching the show...
If you've never been to one of these shows, you might want to buy a ticket.
I hope that people who have never been to a concert like this will think about buying a ticket.
I hope you will think so.
50s
40s
just barely in their 30s
I'm looking forward to having fun with these three of us!
Here they come!
Bringing your own eyefalls
and friendship under the influence of alcohol are prohibited.
Cameras, video cameras, recorders and other recording
Oh, the specifications of the recording device is one side
We'll be leaving now.
The show is about to start.
Are you ready to have a good time?
Let's have some fun.
Congratulations!
The 90th Anniversary Rave Sparked!
Fukuoka Civic Auditorium
Let's have fun!
Congratulations!
Everyone had a great time.
And I will.
Thank you.
I'm so happy
It's so special to be here in Fukuoka.
I can't believe you're here.
I'm glad
Thank you very much
Thank you very much.
Well, by the way...
Maybe I'm having too much fun in Fukuoka.
I'm so happy.
Yesterday?
I went to Riko Ueda's comedy concert.
I went to a comedy concert.
Oh!
Not a sacred place at all.
Shall we get more excited?
Let's dance together!
South Wind Ondo
East is thou
From Chosaka
Good technique
Of the swound
팔
navy
money
Imjing
合随
ne
My feelings have been ken-ken-ken for a long time
There's just too much to look forward to
I'm in love with you
I make it, make it, make it, make it
I can't get mad, I can't get mad, I can't get mad
I'm in love with you
I'm in love with you I'm in love with you
They're laughing at me, who's in love?
Maybe it's never gonna end, you don't know, you don't know how it's gonna be
I'm in love with you
Let's stare at a thing or two
Towards the edge of the mountain
I'm going to go up
I'm on a roll
Prepare for the festival
Coming in the distance
the festival forest
the sound of the wind
dizzying in the wind
The topic of the moment
Moisten the atmosphere
I'll go
Let it go!
Let it go
Let it all cry
Don't believe me.
Fight it
I'm so happy
Time on to shout for a friend
I won't allow it
There's nothing left to wait for
You're wrong, I only like what I like
Gather them in your heart
Towards the dancing gold
I'm in a hurry, I'm in a hurry
I'm going to the bakeshop
Ah ah ah ah
Tonight is tanning day
Zig zagging
I'll never forget
The moments that go by so fast
Overflowing
In the morning when the sky is flying
To ring the bell of light
I'll be glad for the cat
Christmas Eve
Holy!
Holy, Holy, Holy!
Hands on the rim
I'm swaying
I'm so happy
Fingertips touching
So full
Now it's just
Like a blank sheet of paper
Without endurance
Blooming all around
In the biggest days
The divine ornaments are
in flower and summer
even in autumn and winter
it seems to twinkle and sparkle
Nineteen years old
My soul is
filled with
Become a baika
Serve the soul
Already
Three uncles in their 30s, 40s and 50s
thank you for your hard work in entertaining us enough.
It was great.
I guess that's what it means to be burned out!
It's been a while since I've been loud for two hours.
I've never heard a louder voice on the radio.
I know, it doesn't happen like this, but... I feel like I learned a lot by not coming to the show.
I think I learned a lot. I wonder what I learned.
I don't know... there was so much love.
Thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you.
I felt like world peace is here after all!
My back hurts!
You've already got me hooked, haven't you?
Yes, yes, yes...
After this...
Yes.
It's a reaction to happiness.
That's right.
During the show, my watch started to shake.
I put in 10,000 pops.
Wow, wow, wow.
Happiness is in the air.
We're looking forward to our 10th anniversary next year.
I hope you all will support us more and more!
Please support Shoudai Shoujo!
And now, MC Riko Ueda and I, Togi!
We are in charge of Rig Fukuoka Thursday!
Please listen to the radio!
We'll be doing a show called "Gau" afterwards.
We've taken over from Rigu and we're doing it now.
So please continue to listen to the show.
Thank you both very much for your time today.
Thank you very much.
Let's launch the show.
Thank you very much for watching.
A little bit before the show.
I was hoping we could drop a few things before the show.
How did it go?
I thought it was a little bit tighter.
I thought it had a transmitting effect.
The Batten Diet.
It was great.